Lorenzo Collection
Lorenzo Collection
- Allied and associated families
  - Krumbhaar, Helen Ledyard
    - Legal papers
      - Accounts, 1843-1871; 1 item (Box 14)
    - Estate papers
      - Last will and testament and related documents, 1868-1873; 11 items (Box 14)
      - Correspondence related to the settlement of the estate, 1872-1873; 28 items (Box 14)
      - Estate receipts, 1873; 12 items (Box 14)
  - Krumbhaar, Lewis
    - Correspondence with Jonathan D. Ledyard, 1842-1843; 5 items (Box 14)
  - Krumbhaar, George D.
    - Correspondence with Helen L. Fairchild relating to "Lorenzo", 11 items (Box 14)
  - Remington, Eliphalet
    - Papers relating to his Will, 1937; 1 item (Box 14)
    - Obituary notices, 1938; 7 items (Box 14)
  - Remington, Jane Ledyard (Mrs. Eliphalet Remington)
    - Correspondence related to the purchase of the New Jersey lots, 1900-1905; 17 items (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1892-1938; 4 items (Box 14)
    - Maps of the New Jersey lots, 2 items (Box 14)
  - Seymour, Helen Ledyard (Mrs. John Forman Seymour)
    - Will and related paper, undated; 2 items (Box 14)
    - Estate papers, 1881-1883; 10 items (Box 14)
  - Seymour, Horatio Jr.
    - Correspondence, 1906; 2 items (Box 14)
    - Article entitled "Narrow Gauge Rail-roads", 1 item (Box 14)
  - Stebbins, Charles S.
    - Correspondence, 1847-1877; 8 Items (Box 14)
    - Legal and estate papers, 1852-1890; 7 Items (Box 14)
  - Stebbins, Charles S. Jr.
    - Correspondence, 1891; 2 Items (Box 14)
  - Stebbins, Margaret D.
    - Correspondence, 1927; 1 Item (Box 14)
  - Strawbridge, John II
    - Correspondence, 1789-1793; 4 items (Box 14)
    - Eulogy, 1793; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Strawbridge, Hannah Evans (Mrs. John Strawbridge)
    - Correspondence, 1794; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Strawbridge, George (son of John Strawbridge II)
    - Correspondence, undated; 1 item (Box 14)
    - Tax papers, 1820-1821; 1 item (Box 14)
    - Autobiography, undated; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Strawbridge, Joseph (son of John Strawbridge II)
    - Correspondence, 1806-1807; 7 items (Box 14)
  - Strawbridge, Stockton (son of John Strawbridge III and his first wife, Elizabeth Stockton)
    - Correspondence, 1834-1855; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Strawbridge, James (brother of John Strawbridge II)
    - Eulogy, undated; 1 item (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous financial notes, 2 items (Box 14)
  - Wolters, Lambertus
    - Land papers, 1831-1832; 2 items (Box 14)
    - Will and estate papers, 1840; 2 items (Box 14)
- Genealogies
  - Correspondence related to and including family genealogy, 1839-1880; 25 items (Box 15)
  - Ledyard genealogy, 1700-1963; 7 items (Box 15)
  - Forman family genealogy, c.1700-; 5 items (Box 15)
  - Strawbridge genealogy including the Gilpin and Parker families, 1206-; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Background histories on the "Ledyard" name, 3 items (Box 15)
- Ledyard miscellaneous
  - Ledyard cookbook, 1854; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Land Inventories, 1847-1885; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Land sales accounts, 1842-1884; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Photographs of Lorenzo and various members of the family, 6 items (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 1852; 3 items (Box 15)
  - Plan of Lorenzo, 1 item (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous papers
  - Miscellaneous land papers
    - Ledgers, 1868-1874; 2 items (Box 16)
    - Indentures and related land papers, 1787-1888; 64 items (Box 16)
    - Title abstracts, 1827-1868; 4 items (Box 16)
    - Land surveys, 1807-1927; 95 items (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous powers of attorney, 1824-1892; 2 items (Box 16)
    - "A Map of Col. John Lincklaen's Farm (1814)", photocopies pasted on mounting board (Map-case 102)
  - Miscellaneous financial papers
    - Bills and receipts, 1794-1832; 50 items (Box 16)
    - Bonds, 1836-1837; 3 items (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1820-1898; 25 items (Box 16)
    - History of Cazenovia, 1841; 1 item (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous documents related to the Cherry Valley Turnpike, 1803-1860; 3 items (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1860-1956; 8 items (Box 16)
    - Rough Index to the bank folders, 1 item (Box 16)
- Microfilm materials
  - Ledyard and Stebbins Mill Account Book, 1851-1852 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 1)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Travel Accounts, 1884-1886 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 1)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Personal Diaries, 1873-1881 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 1)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Personal Diaries, 1883-1885 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 2)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Journal of a visit to Cuba and Mexico in, 1850 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 3)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Journal of a visit to Chile and California in, 1852 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 4)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Ledger books, 1874-1887 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 5)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Account Books, 1878-1897 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 5)
  - Ledyard Family Letterbook, 1871-1873 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 6)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Letterbook, 1873-1881 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 6)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard Letterbook, 1886-1891 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 6)
  - Holland Land Company Accounts of Land Sales and Census, 1793-1804 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 7)
  - John Lincklaen and Holland Land Company Patents, 1793-1804 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 7)
  - John Lincklaen Letterbook P, 1805-1842 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 7)
  - Ledyard Family Farm Account Books, 1845-1864 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 8)
  - Ledyard Family Farm Ledger Book #2, 1872-1889 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 8)
  - Register of Wisconsin Lands (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 9)
  - Jonathan Denise and Jane Strawbridge Ledyard House and Office Diaries, 1843-1855 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 10)
  - Lambertus Wolters Ledyard House and Office Diary, 1855-1857 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 10)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard and Lambertus Wolters Ledyard House and Office Diaries, 1856-1872 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 10)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard House and Office Diaries, 1872-1887 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 10)
  - George Strawbridge Ledyard, Mary Fitzhugh Ledyard, and Anne Smith Fitzhugh Ledyard House and Office Diaries, 1887-1895 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 11)
  - Holland Land Company Day Books Cazenovia, 1800-1839 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 12)
  - Holland Land Company Day Books Cazenovia, 1840-1865 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 13)
  - Holland Land Company Day Books Cazenovia, 1866-1897 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 14)
  - Holland Land Company General Ledgers, 1802-1806 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 14)
  - Holland Land Company General Ledgers, 1806-1839 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 15)
  - Holland Land Company General Ledgers, 1840-1871 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 16)
  - Holland Land Company General Ledgers, 1872-1897 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 17)
  - Holland Land Company Rough Account Books, 1811-1837 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 17)
  - Holland Land Company Waste Books of Cash and Sales, 1802-1806 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 18)
  - Holland Land Company Cash Books, 1823-1870 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 18)
  - Holland Land Company Lists of Township Land Sales, 1793-1814 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 18)
  - Holland Land Company Land Map Books (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 18)
  - Holland Land Company Land Account Books, 1821-1837 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 18)
  - Holland Land Company Land Account Books, 1838-1884 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 19)
  - Holland Land Company Bond and Mortgage Sales, 1799-1808 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 19)
  - Holland Land Company Township Sale Books for Brakels, DeRuyter and Number 1 Township (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 19)
  - Holland Land Company Township Sale Books (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 20)
  - Ledyard Woolen Mill Financial Books, 1813-1816 (Cabinet 5/3, Reel 20)